Let's talk about the magnified view in image playback.
In order to activate image playback you're going to need to press the button on the furthest side of your camera, at the very bottom left corner there's a blue triangle.
Go ahead and press that button to activate playback mode and what you're going to do is scroll through with your quick control dial and select an image.
I'm going to select that one by pressing set, actually to, it is selected what I'm going to do is zoom in there with the zoom button that looks like a magnifying glass with a plus sign in the middle.
Up here on the top right side of the camera, I'm going to go ahead and press that, now I'm at full size view, and what I want to do is zoom in a little bit further to get closer to see how my, how my focus was and see some of the detail on this image.
Now I'm about as close as I'm going to get.
That's as close as I can zoom in.
That gives me a pretty good idea of the image quality and the sharpness on some of those more contrasted areas of the shot and obviously right now this little indicator in the bottom of the screen is kind of grayed out and there's a white square inside there.
That white square is the image, is the area of the image that I'm zoomed in to.
Right now I'm exactly in the center of the image.
What I can do is use this control just above the quick control dial a little bit to the right of the LCD screen and it kind of acts like a joystick and what I can do is use that to navigate around in my image by pressing in, really any direction and I can scroll around to look at different parts of my image.
I can zoom out and then scroll over to the left.
I can scroll down or diagonally, but what I'm going to do is go ahead and zoom back out, and I was in there pretty close.
Now I'm back to index view.
What I can do is go ahead and select another image and then, and zoom in and check out another image.
It's a good way to check your exposure settings and look at some of the detail on your image.
It's, another thing you can do is get a magnifying glass to place over the top of your LCD screen and look at some of the detail you're getting on your images.